Hilpert, Elmer E. Arbitration Papers 5493
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Staley, A. E., Manufacturing Co. vs. AIW, Local 837, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 9-10)
  8/19/1961
- Staley, A. E., Manufacturing Co. vs. AIW, Local 837, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  2/24/65. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Staley, A. E., Manufacturing Co. vs. AIW, Local 837, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  5/21/65. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Staley, A. E., Manufacturing Co. vs. AIW, Local 837, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  11/8/68. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Staley, A. E., Manufacturing Co. vs. AIW, Local 837, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  7/28/70. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Staley, A. E., Manufacturing Co. vs. AIW, Local 837, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  4/5/71. Issue: arbitration procedure - appeal and review of award
- Staley, A. E., Manufacturing Co. vs. AIW, Local 837, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  1/4/71. Issue: arbitrability; discipline - discharge
- Staley Milling Co. vs. AFGM, Local 167, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  11/9/56. Issue: arbitrability; testing of employees - qualifications
- Standard Gravure Corp. vs. Louisville Photo-Engravers Union No. 30, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  5/15/65. Issue: arbitrability
- Standard Oil Co. vs. Central States Petroleum Union, Local 115, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  10/10/58. Issue: overtime
- Standard Oil Co. vs. Central States Petroleum Union, Local 115, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  10/15/58. Issue: vacancies - temporary.
- Standard Oil Co. vs. Central States Petroleum Union, Local 115, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  10/18/58. Issue: schedules of work - notice.
- Standard Oil Co. vs. Central States Petroleum Union, Local 115, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  10/31/58. Issue: vacancies - seniority
- Standard Oil Co., Wood River, Illinois vs. Central States Petroleum Union, Local 115, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  10/30/58. Issue: schedules of work - remedy for improper change
- Standard Pipe protection, Inc. vs. USA, Local 6033, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  2/15/59. Issue: vacation pay - layoff.
- Standard Pipe protection, Inc. vs. USA, Local 5066., 1960 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  3/22/60. Issue: layoff
- Standard Pipe protection, Inc. vs. USA, Local 5066., 1960 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  11/7/60. Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime.
- Standard Pipe protection, Inc. vs. USA, Local 6104, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  9/6/63. Issue: probationary employees - holidays and holiday pay
- Standard Pipe protection, Inc. vs. USA, Local 5066, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  4/30/65. Issue: rates of pay
- Steelcase Manufacturing Co. vs. Paintmakers' and Warehousemen's Union, Local 604, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  10/10/60. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Steelcase Manufacturing Co. - Paint and Allied Industries Employers Group vs. Paintmakers' and Warehousemen's Union, Local 604, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  9/16/63. Issue: holidays and holiday pay - vacations
- Stein Egg and Poultry Co., Inc. vs. Miscellaneous Drivers and Helpers, Local 610, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  6/5/67. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Sterling National Industries, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 309, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  11/20/58. Issue: assignment of jobs - rates of pay
- Sterling Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 1095, 1953 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  9/26/53. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Sterling Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 1095, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  6/24/54. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Sterling Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 1095, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  3/24/57. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Sterling Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 1095, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  4/30/57. Issue: assignment of jobs - qualifications
- Sterling Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 1095, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  6/18/60. Issue: layoff - seniority; reinstatement - seniority
- Sterling Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 1095, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  9/21/61. Issue: workweek - decrease
- Stewart-Warner Corp., John W. Hobbs Corp. Division vs. UAW, Local 1235, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  2/28/64. Issue: layoff - ability vs. seniority.
- Stewart-Warner Corp., John W. Hobbs Corp. Division vs. UAW, Local 1235, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  10/8/65. Issue: past practice - working conditions
- Stewart-Warner Corp., John W. Hobbs Corp. Division vs. UAW, Local 1235, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  5/26/67. Issue: discipline - suspensions
- Stewart-Warner Corp., John W. Hobbs Corp. Division vs. UAW, Local 1235, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  7/21/66. No decision
- Stewart-Warner Corp., John W. Hobbs Corp. Division vs. UAW, Local 1235, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  12/20/67. Issue: overtime
- Stewart-Warner Corp., John W. Hobbs Corp. Division vs. UAW, Local 1235 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  No date. No decision
- Stix, Baer and Fuller Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  1/16/67. Issue: contracting out - layoff
- Suburban Delivery Co., Associated Retailers vs. IBT, Local 688, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  12/11/71. Issue: arbitrability -timeliness; termination of employment
- Super Valu Stores, Inc. vs. Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 394., 1971 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  8/8/71. Issue: funeral leave and funeral pay.
- Swift and Co., Muskogee, Oklahoma vs. MCBW, Food handlers Local 425, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  3/15/68. No decision.
- Tappan Co. vs. UAW, Local 1068, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  10/27/67. Issue: rates of pay - incentive pay
- Tappan Co. vs. UAW, Local 1068, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  7/29/69. Settled
- Tenn-Flake of Middlesboro, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 783, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  9/21/68. Issue: contract interpretation - rates of pay - reporting pay
- Tenn-Tex Alloy Corp. of Houston vs. USA, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  6/25/69. Settled
- Tenneco Oil Co. vs. OCAW, Local 4-522., 1967 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  10/2/67. Issue: posting and job classification. (Settled.)
- Terre Haute Malleable and Manufacturing Corp. vs. Int'l Molders and Foundry Workers Union of North America, Local 265, 1962 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  1/12/62. Issue: classification of jobs - new machinery
- Texaco, Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 7-368, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  6/7/60. Issue: failure to call-in
- Texaco, Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 4-23, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  2/29/60. Issue: job classification - evaluation of job factors - rates of pay
- Texaco, Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 4-23, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  10/13/67. Withdrawn
- Texaco, Inc., 1968 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  4/19/68. No award
- Texaco, Inc. vs. Petroleum Trade Employees Union, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  7/10/70. Issue: discharge - arbitrability - timeliness
- Texas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 4-23, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  1/15/57. Issue: rate of pay - claim for pay of a higher classification.
- Texas Co. vs. OCAW, Local 4-23, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  8/28/57. Issue: change of job duties
- Texas Electric Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 2228, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  7/26/68. Issue: discharge - insubordination - profanity
- Texas Electrical Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 2228, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  8/2/68. Issue: holiday pay
- Texas - U. S. Chemical Co. vs. OCAW, Local 4-228, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  10/12/66. Issue: assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification.
- Textile Paper Products, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 50, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  8/10/66. Issue: holiday pay
- Textron, Inc., Randall Co. vs. UAW, Local 1249, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  7/10/66. Issue: arbitrability - cost of arbitration; claim for pay of a higher classification
- Textron Co., Burkart-Randall Plant vs. IAM, Local 1076, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  11/9/70. Issue: oral agreement
- Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Co. vs. GBBA, Local 42, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  12/28/63. Issue: holiday pay
- Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Co. vs. GBBA (Box 84, Folder 21)
  No award.
- Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Co. vs. GBBA (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Thomas J. Lipton, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 838, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  12/16/71. Issue: differentials in pay - vacation pay
- Thoms Pontiac, Inc. vs. Automobile Transport Chauffeurs, Demonstrators and Helpers, IBT, Local 604, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  4/30/60. Issue: failure to recall.
- Tubular Steel, Inc. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, IBT, Local 688, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  11/7/60. Issue: layoff - discipline - discrimination
- Twin City Barge and Towing Co. vs. Marine Officers Association, IBT, Local 54, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  8/31/68. Issue: progressive discipline
- Unimet Corp. vs. USA, Local 7512, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  10/15/71. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Union Bag-Camp Paper Corp. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 762, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  11/30/67. Issue: demotions.
- Union Carbide Corp., Metals Division vs. OCAW, Local, 3-639, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 3-4)
  4/30/65. Issue: assignment of jobs - qualifications
- Union Carbide Corp., Metals Division vs. OCAW, Local, 3-639, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  4/4/66. Issue: classification of jobs - assignment of work outside classification
- Union Carbide Corp., Metals Division vs. OCAW, Local, 3-639, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  3/6/66. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Union Carbide Corp., Metals Division vs. OCAW, Local, 3-639, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  3/31/66. Issue: discipline - suspension
- Union Carbide Corp., Metals Division vs. OCAW, Local, 3-639, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  4/7/66. Issue: overtime
- Union Carbide Corp., Metals Division vs. OCAW, Local, 3-639 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Union Carbide Corp., Metals Division vs. OCAW, Local, 3-639, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  5/10/66. Issue: rates of pay - classification of jobs
- Union Carbide Corp., Nuclear Division vs. OCAW, Local 3-288, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  6/18/68. Withdrawn
- Union Carbide Corp., Materials Systems Division, Stellite Works vs. USA, Local 2958, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  8/30/68. Issue: holidays and holiday pay -shift differentials
- Union Carbide Corp., Materials Systems Division, Stellite Works vs. USA, Local 2958, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  11/15/68. Issue: arbitration procedure - appeal and review of award
- Union Starch and Refining Co., Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 7-663, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  1/25-26/60. No decision.
- Union Starch and Refining Co., Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 7-663, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  5/9/60. Issue: rates of pay
- Union Starch and Refining Co., Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 7-663, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  7/19/60. Issue: rates of pay - increases
- Union Tank Car, Smith and Loveless Inc. Division vs. USA, Local 5301, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- United Nuclear Corp., Chemicals Division vs. Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  5/15/62. Issue: discipline - layoff
- United Press Int'l. vs. Wire Service Guild (Box 85, Folder 19)
- United States Defense Corp. vs. IBEW, Local 1, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  2/3/58. Issue: rates of pay
- United States Pipe and Foundry, Bessemer Pipe Plant vs. IAM, Lodge 125 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- United States Pipe and Foundry, Birmingham, Alabama vs. IMAW, Local 256, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  12/27/72. Issue: discipline - warnings
- U. S. Pipe and Foundry Co., North Birmingham, Alabama vs. IMAW, Local 256, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  9/30/74. Issue: termination of employment - inability
- U. S. Plywood - Champion Papers, Inc. vs. UPP, Local 1967, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  11/15/68. Withdrawn
- U. S. Plywood - Champion Papers, Inc. vs. IWA, Local 5-355, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  7/14/72. Issue: discipline -discharge - insubordination
- U. S. Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 4246, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  11/15/53. Issue: assignment of work - temporary
- U. S. Steel Co. vs. CLGW, Local 205, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  4/5/67. No award
- Valley Steel Products Co. vs. IBT, Local 50, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  12/4/61. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Valley Steel Products Co. vs. USA, Local 680., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  1/7/63. Issue: discipline - discharge - misconduct during layoff status
- Valley Steel Products co. IBT, Local 50, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  9/26/66. Issue: seniority - date of eligibility
- Valspar Corp. vs. Paintmakers and Warehouse Workers, Local 604, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  12/8/61. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Valspar Corp. vs. Paintmakers and Warehouse Workers, Local 604, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  11/11/62. Issue: discipline - discharge - misconduct
- Valspar Corp. vs. Paintmakers and Warehouse Workers, Local 604, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  10/14/63. Issue: discipline - layoff - sleeping on the job
- Vandalia Bus Lines, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 729, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  8/4/61. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Vendo Co. vs. USA, Local 4803, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  6/12/63. Issue: evaluation of jobs - classification of jobs
- Vess Bottling Co. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  7/17/62. Issue: assignment of jobs - temporary assignment - posting of jobs
- Vestal Laboratories, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  4/25/63. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Vogt, Henry, Machine Co. vs. USA, Local 1693, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  4/12/65. Issue: assignment of jobs - outside bargaining unit
- Vogt, Henry, Machine Co. vs. USA, Local 1693, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  2/16/70. Issue: discipline - discharge - alcoholism
- Vogt, Henry, Machine Co. vs. USA, Local 1693, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  5/14/70. No award
- Vogt, Henry, Machine Co. vs. USA, Local 1693, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  7/26/72. Issue: schedules of work - overtime
- Vollmar Brothers Construction Co. vs. IBT, Local 682, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  3/20/70. Issue: discipline - discharge - timeliness
- Von Weiss Gear Co. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  11/21/64. Issue: discipline - discharge - leaving work area without permission
- Waggener Paint Co. vs. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America and Paint, Varnish and Lacquer Makers Union, Local 754, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  9/15/66. Withdrawn.
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  1/29/65. Issue: overtime
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  1/31/65. Issue: overtime - remedy for improper assignment
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  2/4/66. Issue: management rights - creation of new classification
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  10/20/66. Settled
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  5/12/67. Issue: rates of pay - incentive pay.
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  1/6/67. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 7-8)
  1/6/69. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  2/9/69. Issue: classification of jobs - change in work assignments
- Wagner Castings Co. vs. AIW, Local 728, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  5/18/69. Issue: classification of jobs - assignment to work outside classification
- Wagner Electric Brake and Clutch Co. vs. USA, Local 3245, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  8/24/68. Issue: overtime - assignment of jobs.
- Wagner Electric Corp., St. Louis, Missouri vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 23, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 12-13)
  1/12/61. Issue: classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors
- Wagner Electric Co. vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  (Continued from Box 87.)
- Wagner Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 1104, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  6/10/69. Issue: classification of job
- Wagner Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 1104, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  8/30/69. Issue: classification of job
- Wagner Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 1104, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  9/6/69. Issue: classification of job
- Wagner Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 1104, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  10/12/69. Issue: rates of pay - incentive pay.
- Wagner Electric Co. vs. IBEW, Local 2140, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 7-9)
  5/17/71. Issue: discipline - discharge - improper job attitude
- Wagner Electric vs. IUE, Local 1104, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  10/30/73. Issue: discipline - discharge - alcoholism
- Wagner Electric vs. IUE, Local 1104, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  4/22/74. Issue: discipline - discharge - failure to meet standards of production
- Wagner Electric Corp., Brinkley, Arkansas vs. IBEW, Local 240, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  2/16/75. Issue: union representatives and business - discrimination
- Walker Manufacturing Co. - Distribution Center vs. SEIU, Local 150-T, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  4/11/71. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Weather-Proof Co., Litchfield, Illinois vs. IAM, District 123, Local 878, 1959 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  7/7/59. Issue: rates of pay - equal pay for equal work
- Weather-Proof Co., Litchfield, Illinois vs. IAM, District 123, Local 878, 1964 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  6/22/64. Issue: overtime -Saturday, Sunday and holiday work
- Weber Dental Manufacturing Co. vs. UE, Local 745., 1953 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  1/23/53. No decision
- Weber Dental Manufacturing Co. vs. UE, Local 745., 1955 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  6/14/55. Issue: discipline - layoffs
- Weber Dental Manufacturing Co. vs. UE, Local 745., 1955 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  6/20/55. Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime
- Western Auto Supply Co. vs. Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Industries Employees Union, Local 618, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  11/10/72. Issue: arbitrability; fringe benefits - in-plant feeding
- Western Electric Co., Inc. - Installation Organization, Atlanta-West Area vs. CWA, Local 3290, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 9-10)
  12/23/62. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Western Electric Corp. vs. Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 11-13)
  10/14/70. Issue: promotions
- Western Electric Co. vs. CWA, Local 6290, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1-4)
  9/26/73. Issue: discipline - discharge - police record
- Western Stoneware Co. vs. UBCW, Local 906, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  4/13/56. Issue: vacation pay
- Western Textile Products Co. vs. United Textile Workers of America (UTWA), Local 179, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 6-7)
  6/14/60. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Western Union Telegraph Co. vs. Commercial Telegraphers Union, Western Union Division, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  12/22/60. Issue: bidding - qualifications.
- Western Union Telegraph Co. vs. Commercial Telegraphers Union, Western Union Division, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  12/31/60. Issue: vacancies - seniority; grievance and grievance procedure - dismissal
- Western Union Telegraph Co. vs. Commercial Telegraphers Union, Southwestern Division, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  7/12/65. Issue: arbitrability - jurisdiction.
- Western Union Telegraph Co. vs. Commercial Telegraphers Union, Southwestern Division, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  7/4/66. Issue: arbitrability - timeliness; overtime
- Westinghouse Electric Corp., Birmingham, Alabama vs. IBEW, Local 1871, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  8/14/59. Issue: funeral leave and funeral leave pay
- Westinghouse Electric Corp., Columbus, Ohio vs. IUE, Local 746, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  3/7/63. Issue: discipline - layoff.
- Westinghouse Electric Corp., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania vs. IBEW, Local 2109, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  12/9/68. Settled.
- Westinghouse Electric Corp., Lima, Ohio vs. Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 7-8)
  4/27/70. Issue: assignment of jobs - qualifications
- Westinghouse Electric Corp., Lima, Ohio vs. Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  6/26/70. Issue: promotion. (No decision.)
- Westinghouse Electric Corp., Birmingham, Alabama vs. IBEW, Local 1871, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  12/5/70. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Westinghouse Electric Corp., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  2/22/74. No decision.
- Wetterau Foods, Inc. vs. General Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local 21 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  8/4/69. Issue: guaranteed workweek.
- White Motor Corp. vs. IAM, District 9. (Box 92, Folder 2)
  6/22/73. Issue: creation of a new classification - unilateral action; rate of pay
- Wholesale Furniture Co. vs. Department Store, Furniture and Appliance Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, IBT, Local 709 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  4/7/62. Issue: discharge - management rights - prior record, misconduct
- Wince Manufacturing Co., Inc. vs. USA, Local 4452 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  2/12/59. Issue: discharge - intoxication and insubordination
- Wisconsin Tissue Mills vs. UPIU, Local 1279 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  11/24/74. Issue: discharge - off-duty misconduct -assaults
- Wood River Processing Crop. vs. USA, Local 3643 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  2/24/72. Issue: discipline - reprimand - procedural due process
- Woods Industries vs. IBT, Local 498 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  6/61. No award.
- Wrought Washer Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 1673 (Box 92, Folder 8-9)
  5/18/61. Issue: interest arbitration - rates of pay - overtime
- Wyandotte Chemical Corp., Geismar, Louisiana vs. OCAW, Local 4-620 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  5/4/61. Issue: rates of pay - past practice.
- Wyandotte Chemical Corp., Geismar, Louisiana vs. OCAW, Local 4-620 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  12/6/64. Issue: discipline - refusal of overtime
- Yuba Heat Transfer Corp. vs. Ironworkers, Local 620 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  7/23/68. No decision
- Yung and Mueller Bakery Co. vs. Salesmen and Delivery Men of Bakery Products, IBT, Local 611 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  6/7/52. Issue: rates of pay